fumikomu ze akuseru
press down hard on the gas
kakehiki wa nai sa sou dayo
that's right, there's no compromise
yoru wo nukeru
we'll slip through the night
nejikomu sa saigo ni
at the final moment push hard
sashihiki zero sa sou dayo
that's right, all the way to zero
hibi wo kezuru
until we wipe away the days
kokoro wo sotto
gently open your heart
hiraite gyutto
hiki yosetara
if you pull it close to you
todoku yo kitto
it will reach you, without a doubt
tsutau yo motto sa aa
it will come, closer, now
iki isoide shiboritotte
we're speeding through life, squeezing it for all of its worth
motsureru ashi
our feet are tied
dakedo mae yori zutto sou tooku he
but we still keep going further
ubaitotte tsukandatte
even if I take it back, and grasp it
kimi janai nara
if you're not the one
imi wa nai no sa
there will be no meaning
dakara haruka kanata
and so we'll go far off into the distance
Sasuke-kun!
Naruto's certainly different
from you, Sasuke-kun.
He's a klutz and kind of gets in the way.
But he's not in the least a coward!
Right? Isn't that's right?!
Sasuke-kun!
You foolish younger brother.
If you want to kill me, resent me,
hate me and...
continue to live your ugly life.
No...
Flee.
Flee and hang on to your life.
No!
Revive,
Sharingan!
Finish Move -
Fire Element,
Dragon Fire
Technique!
Just what I expect of the Uchiha clan...
His blood has begun to stir...
I should take my time and
confirm his true power.
I have to live so I can kill
my older brother...
That's what I thought.
But it's me who was being stupid.
— Naruto!
— Sakura!
How can someone who can't put
his life on the line at a place like this...
beat that man?!
I can see.
I can see!
I can see you!
It's pretty good...
You foretell my movements and
your aim is sure.
You can see my moves, can't you?
The sun will set soon...
I must find him quickly!
It will become completely dark
and my disadvantage will increase.
But why in the world right now...
what's his goal?
Well, that's fine...
He came to this village.
I'll settle this here and now.
I got you!
A substitution!
Sasuke-kun!
Humph!
You are too easy.
The Uchiha name is crying.
That's okay.
I'll just take my time and play
with you before I'll kill you.
Like a worm.
This is Sharingan Windmill Triple Attack!
Fire Style: Dragon Flame Jutsu.
He did it!
Sasuke-kun!
You did it!
Are you okay?
Hang on.
Paralysis?
I didn't expect that you could use
Sharingan this much at your age.
You are truly a member
of the Uchiha clan.
I do want you, after all.
You're definitely his brother.
Your eyes hide more ability
than that Itachi.
Who in the world are you?
My name is Orochimaru...
If you think you want to meet me again,
desperately run to the top of this test.
— The Scroll!
— Defeat the three...
Sound Village Ninja
under my control.
You are not making sense at all!
We don't want to see
your face ever again, got it?!
That won't do.
Sasuke-kun!
You, what did you do to Sasuke-kun?
I gave him a parting gift.
Sasuke-kun absolutely would
come look for me...
looking for power.
I enjoyed seeing your various powers.
Sasuke-kun!
Hold on, Sasuke-kun.
C'mon!
Sasuke-kun...
Sasuke-kun, c'mon!
Naruto!
Sasuke-kun's... Sasuke-kun's...!
What?
What should I do?
I can feel it!
He's close by.
It's been a while...
Anko.
You're level S class,
an extremely dangerous person on
the most wanted list.
That's why I'll kill you here
even if it costs my life.
That is my duty as
your former subordinate
who learned it all from you.
Isn't that right, Orochimaru?!
No, you can't.
Striking Shadow Snake!
I won't let you escape.
I got you.
Orochimaru,
I'm gonna borrow your left hand.
This hand sign...
Right... you and I are going to die here.
Ninja Art: Twin Snakes Sacrifice...
You intend to commit suicide?
Substitution.
As you are a Special Jonin
of the village,
you can't be just using
the forbidden Jutsu I taught you.
I told you it wouldn't work.
Why have you come now?
It's our reunion after so long,
and you're awfully cold.
Don't tell me that you came
to assassinate Hokage-sama?
No, no...
I don't have enough
subordinates for that yet...
I've heard of the excellence ones of
this village and thought I'd put dibs on it.
A little while ago,
I gave that same Curse Mark
as a present.
There's a kid that I want.
Selfish as always.
That kid will die.
Certainly... the odds are 1 in 10
that he'll die,
but he may survive just like you did.
This kid, you really like him, huh?
Are you jealous?.
Hey...
Are you still holding a grudge
that I used you and threw you away?
Unlike you, that kid will excel.
For one thing he inherited
the Uchiha ability.
He has beautiful features and is
a vessel who can become my heir.
If that kid lived,
it will make things interesting.
Be sure not to cancel this test.
Three people from my village
are also under your care.
Make me enjoy it.
If something happens to
deprive me of my fun,
consider it the end of Leaf Village.
We've secured food and water after
spending half a day
and now most teams have halted activity.
As we planned,
this is the time that we attack.
We'll split up into three and go scouting.
However, whether we find
other teams or not,
we return to this place.
Got it?
Okay.
Roger.
Scatter!
His breathing is gradually
getting regular...
but he still has a terrible fever.
I have to protect them both.
I have to communicate this
to Hokage-sama right away.
Damn! At a time like this!
T-This is Paralysis Jutsu.
So you are here, Anko.
You're pretty late for ANBU Black Ops.
Well, don't say that.
Are you okay, hey?
Huh? T-This is...!
The Curse Mark is appearing...
Don't tell me...?!
Is it Orochimaru?
What, really?
Now that it's come to this,
we'll take you to Hokage-sama.
No, take me to the tower.
What are you saying?
The moment Orochimaru comes
to this village,
a strict alert is issued.
It's more urgent than
continuing the Exam.
I know...
Anyway, I'll tell the whole story later,
so please call for Hokage-sama.
I found you.
As Orochimaru-sama ordered,
we'll wait for daybreak to do it.
Uchiha Sasuke is our target,
not the other.
If they come in the way,
it's okay to kill the other two, right?
Of course.
hey, can you hear it?
nee kikoe masu ka
sora wa hate shinaku aoku sunde ite
the clear, blue sky goes on and on
umi wa kagiri naku koudai de ite
the ocean spans limitlessly
kimi wa itsumade mo egao de ite
please keep that smile on your face forever
janai to nai chau kara
or else I'll cry
mawari o mimawasa naku temo
You won't have to search around you
mou iin da yo
it's all ok now
kono to no naka ni wa minna ga iru kara
everyone is inside this hand
naki taku natte nige taku natte
when you want to cry, and you want to run away
shiawase o wasure te te shimatta ra
when you forget what happiness is
mina utae
just sing
hikari ga umare yami ga umare ta
light is born, and darkness was born
futatsu wa hitotsu
the two are one
HARUMONIA kanji Te TEREPASHII
harmonia, feel the telepathy
nee kikoe masu ka
hey, can you hear it?
The beautiful wild beast of Leaf Village,
Rock Lee, is here!
Yeah, I did it!
I did it, Guy-sensei!
Now I can get Sakura-san's heart,
right on the mark!
You could say, in terms of numbers,
the disadvantage is mine!
But on the contrary,
the conditions have been met.
Guy-sensei, I will use that technique
without hesitation.
Next episode:
"Super Eyebrow Platonic! I Will Protect You to the Death!!"